

Matteo Santoro

FullStack Develope

- San Vito Dei Normanni, 72019, Italy
- 3337360501
- https://viveresenzalattosio.it
- MatthewSaintbull

SKILLS

JS (React/Node/Vue)

4 years experience at work

AWS

4 years experience at work +

Docker

GIT

Python

My first programming language

C++

Hobbyist

Metasploit

Hobbyist

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Developer Associate

(08/2018)

CISCO CCNP R&S

(05/2016)

CISCO IOE

(06/2016)

CISCO

CISCO

CISCO CCNA 1

(06/2015)

LANGUAGES

Italian

English

tive B2 - Technical • • • • • •

I have been passionate about computer science since the age of seven and started my studies at ITT G. Giorgi, where I obtained three CISCO certifications. After completing my studies at the Poggiolevante merit college in Bari, I attended the Computer Science course at the University of Bari and, thanks to the college, I also participated in various courses in Android, C++, Java, and PHP. I also obtained a soft skills certification and gained experience in team working through a project for an IT company in Bisceglie. After two years at university, I began working as a junior developer at Fincons Group and obtained the AWS Developer certificate. In September 2019, I joined YOOX-Net-A-Porter Group as a developer, working with custom cms and react/aws technologies. In 2021, I started a new career as a Full Stack Developer @ Doveconviene.it. From there I moved to SAVI Italia as a software engineer in an international team

WORK EXPERIENCE

Transcribr

(01/2022 - Present)

Founder

Thanks to my new freelance experience, I am working on a startup that aims to enhance the Learning Management Systems adding Artificial Intelligence Improvements.

Freelancer (12/2023 - Present)

Team Manager and Fullstack Developer

As a freelancer I am collaborating with Brain SRL, following the development of an e-commerce and coordinating the team tasks

SAVI Italia (06/2022 - 12/2022)

Software Engineer

As a member of the International Team, using **nodejs/VueJS** my duty was to mantain with the other colleagues, the softwares and web apps related to Offers/Coupons/Cashback (mainly code coverage and tests development)

Shopfully (06/2021 - 06/2022)

Full Stack Developer

As a member of the 'Platform Team', using nodejs, phpand ReactJS over the AWS infrastructure (using Serverless Framework for the IAAC) I worked on internal projects that aimed to enhance the experience for our marketing team, such as the Campaign Manager; A tool used by them to create and handle all the campaigns in Doveconviene.it, calling the google adv. api

Yoox Net-A-Porter Group

(08/2019 - 05/2021)

AWS Developer

My main role in Yoox was to setup and create all the **Special Campaigns** during the year, such as Christmas or Black Friday campaign. Using **JQuery**, **ReactJS** and **NodeJS**, I had to improve and refactor the content manager software, taking advantage of my skills and certification as an **AWS Developer**.

Fincons Group

(03/2018 - 08/2019)

Developer

As a Junior Developer Consultant I worked for important companies around the world, using Java (Spring) + Aws. There I had the chance to certificate myself as AWS Developer and started my career in the cloud.

SIDE PROJECTS

Vivere senza lattosio

A blog regarding the Lactose Intolerance using HugoCMS

https://viveresenzalattosio.it

GamerNerd

Using the rss parser, it fetches latest news from important websites and shows it

https://gamernerd.it

Vue Rss Parsify

Rss parser client side

https://www.npmjs.com/package/@saintbull/vue-rss-parsify

KalliztoCSS

CSS Library for my own projects

https://github.com/MatthewSaintBull/kallizto

EDUCATION

Università degli studi di Bari Aldo Moro

(08/2016 - 08/2018)

Computer Science

unfinished

Because I had the opportunity to start my career while I was in college, I left my studies since I felt I was already ready to work.